hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and we haven't met
yet I help coaches trainers mentors and
course creators scale their businesses
to six seven and eight figures and I
want to help you even if you're just
getting started get off on the right
foot the right way and that's what we're
going to talk about today what are the
most profitable niches for your business
or as I say niches I I know you can say
it either way
you'll hear me say niches from here on
out and so here's how we find the most
profitable niches the first thing that
I'm going to tell you is this
is you gotta shift your mindset about
niches and about the niche for your
coaching or course okay
but before we go into that I just want
to tell you that
course creation and coaching is one of
the fastest ways for you to make money
on the internet you don't need a lot of
startup costs you don't need to
manufacture anything and you can find
customers very easily using simple tools
and strategies that we teach you on this
podcast and so if that's you you're in
the right place I'd love to Mentor you
I'd love to work with you this podcast
is designed to be a resource to Mentor
people that maybe they're not ready yet
to join my group coaching program but
they want to get the strategies to get
started and to start making money and so
there's over 190 episodes of the podcast
there's over a thousand videos on my
YouTube channel as well which are on
specific issue topics that course
creators and coaches are dealing with
and so make sure to plug into that if
you're a course creator if you're a
coach nearly every topic that you could
imagine that you could deal with I've
made some kind of a video on and so you
can search for the the topic that you're
dealing with and and Jeremiah Krakowski
in the YouTube search bar you know how
like you search videos and I'm sure
you'll find five to ten different videos
that I've created and I'm continuing to
make videos based off of the feedback of
this audience and so there's a specific
video that you'd love to for me to make
a topic on or make a podcast episode on
let me know you guys are the ones that
decide what these videos are and I'm
constantly asked from people what are
the most profitable niches how can I
find which one would work best for me
so back to this the truth is you know
the niche that you're going to start
with is not always going to be your
Forever Niche because a lot of people
will start with one thing and then
realize a Their audience actually wants
something that's slightly different and
they're willing to pay more money for
something that's slightly different so
be fluid when it comes to the process of
picking a niche because if you're not
fluid in that process you can get stuck
mentally feeling like you're you're just
Treading Water you're just spinning your
wheels you're just trying to figure out
what the best thing is and and you get
three steps forward
two steps back three steps forward four
steps back and this is one of the number
one areas that I notice a lot of people
when they discover online coaching and
courses
they get stuck
as a six step process that I walk my
paid clients through and the first step
of that process is picking your Niche
now you got to pick something because
you can't do the rest of the work
without actually picking a profitable
Niche and so this really is the first
step
one of the number one reasons why people
don't end up picking their niches
they're worried about it being the wrong
one or they're worried about it not
being profitable or they're worried
about wasting time or maybe you say well
I'm not worried about it but I just want
to make sure it's the right thing I get
that
and so I want to tell you that usually
when it comes to picking your Niche
you're gonna pick something that might
not be 100 perfect you don't want to
focus on it being perfect but rather it
being good enough and this is a huge
thing that I encourage people in is
picking a niche that is good enough to
get you started to get the ball rolling
to start to actually build an offer to
get leads to grow your email list and
then to start to get paid clients that's
the process and that's the that's the
six step process that we walk people
through is Step number one you pick the
niche okay step number two you write the
offer copy the sales copy the words that
are on an offer and and the number one
thing that you need to do is promote
offers that get people onto an email
list using software like MailChimp okay
MailChimp is an auto responder or
software that you can get
maybe 50 or 100 people onto a a database
and then you can mass email people about
what it is that you're selling and this
is the process that creates six seven
and eight figure businesses is growing
an email list there's not there's one
activity that matters more than
everything else
is growing your email list and so but to
grow your email list you need to have an
offer around a specific topic that
people want and so that's what we're
talking about today is how do you find
that most profitable topic for you I've
been teaching this for quite a bit
that's why this episode is probably one
of the most condensed best resources
that's going to help you get started I'm
gonna I might have sent you this as a
link I'm going to refer to this often
and so again I want you to Big Picture
get the six steps down finding your
Niche is Step number one we're going to
go into that here in just a second
creating your offer copy it's the words
that are on a on a web page where people
give you their name and email address
because you're you're promising them
some kind of a result you're going to
give them either an ebook or a master
class or they're going to join a virtual
event for you by the way Live Events are
what we use because they produce the
most amount of trust in our audience and
and those convert to sales the most
often that's part of our framework that
we teach people but ultimately your
offer copy is related to whatever Niche
you pick and then you create a landing
page where they sign up you build out
the funnel and you promote that funnel
to people through Facebook ads organic
and social media content and that's the
process that we teach people that's the
process that I work with people through
is how to go through really crafting
that messaging really coming up with
what those words are because most people
get stuck in that process of okay I
found my Niche but how do I actually
make sure that I get leads at the right
cost if we're running paid ads because
we teach you how to run paid ads paid
advertising on Facebook Instagram and
tick tock because you're able to find
people that you've never met before get
them to join you on a zoom call this is
our whole process that we use we have
people join us on a zoom call and it's
usually like 50 to 100 people at a time
joining us on a zoom call
for instance this last month I got 50
people to join me on a zoom call
and we got 30 of them to sign up for my
coaching program we made over a hundred
and sixty thousand dollars this month in
our business
by doing this simple process and so
maybe you're like I don't want to make
160 000 this month I just want to make
16 000. I just want to make 6 000 is the
same process and so even if you just got
10 people on a zoom call with you
generally you'll need to get about 30
people registered for about 10 people on
a zoom call and you can usually sell
about
two to five of whatever it is you're
offering
your paid ads cost to get about 30
people on a zoom call is gonna uh 30
people to register and 10 on the zoom
calls gonna cost you on the high end you
know it might it might cost you 300 to
500 but if that 300 to 500 turned into
three thousand to five thousand you see
how that can become a business right
there because if you invest 300 into a
Facebook ad campaign and this is these
are actual results my client Angie who's
in our group actually did this exact
these exact numbers she spent 300 on
paid ads made five thousand dollars and
so this process works this is what we've
been using for for years it's just kind
of changed a little bit but I digress
let's go back to picking the most
profitable Niche because it it is true
the riches are in the niches now you're
going to
get more specific about your niche as
you progress for me and my business
I started with
all people on the internet that was I I
went into the business in 2018 and I was
like okay everybody who's on the
internet I want to help them make money
I know how to help them make money
and and and I helped a lot of people do
that but I didn't make the kind of money
that I'm making now until I really honed
into
course creators and coaches that want to
dial in their messaging and use paid ads
to scale their business those are the
people that that's like that's my group
of people if I can find as many coaches
and course creators that want to use
paid ads and they want to make a lot of
money as possible if I can get as many
of them on a zoom call
they usually end up becoming a client of
mine because we deliver so much value we
deliver so much results for them we make
it very simple
and and if that's you if you're somebody
that you're saying okay I want to run
paid ads I want to build a coaching or a
course business
that's what this podcast is for
and so picking your most profitable
Niche really starts with this is
answering this question
who do you want to help
see a niche is all about who the person
is not what you're teaching and that's
one of the most common misconceptions is
that people think
that the niches what you teach somebody
it's actually who you're helping it's
actually who is the person
that is looking for a desired result and
your offer copy is once you identify who
that person is
you want to identify what is the problem
they have
and the solution the end result that you
can coach them on or train them on or
teach them about
and so then that leads you to you create
a course
that then you can mark it
what we recommend is that you make a
course that has q a attached to it and
you sell it for a thousand dollars you
might say that sounds expensive great
discount it by 70 percent
for the first two times you launch it
sell it for 300 you're gonna sell a ton
of them and you'll be able to make at
least enough money by selling it for 300
to make back your ad spend you might not
be very profitable at 300. but you'll
make back your Aspen and you'll grow in
confidence
if you want to be profitable at the gate
I recommend you sell your course in
coaching for a minimum of a thousand
dollars because that price point a it's
not really that expensive for the right
person the right Prospect the like the
like the right person who's looking to
have a problem solved if I'm saying
listen I'm going to show you how to
build a six-figure coaching business
and I sell that for a thousand dollars
that's a pretty good value for the
results especially with me delivering
that result to people and so whatever it
is that you're offering a thousand
dollars your consumer your prospect your
prospective student is gonna see that as
a really good value and so your job is
how do I market and then sell to as many
of those people as possible and that's
what I coach people on and that's what
we work with people on and that's what
this podcast is dedicated to words
so when it comes to picking the most
profitable niche
you want to look at who do you want to
help what problem do they have and what
solution would you like to lead them to
and then you can build an offer around
that so this is where a lot of people
get it wrong is they think that they map
out their coaching program they map out
their course they map out their lessons
they pre-record them and they build all
this stuff before launching it it's the
worst thing to do it that's the worst
way to do it it's that'll keep you broke
you're not going to have the kind of
impact that you want to have by doing
that okay
for you to have the kind of impact that
you want to have and make the kind of
money that you want to make you have to
start with creating an offer that gets
people on your email list that you can
write to and send additional offers too
your income is related to how often you
ask people to buy from you something
and you fill your pipeline with new
people
by doing this and you move them up what
we call an Ascension model you ascend
people up a value ladder or maybe they
might buy from UA
a seven dollar mini class
but then in the mini class you sell them
on your your 297 dollar master class and
then in that 297 Master Class you sell
them on your your three thousand dollar
group coaching program and then inside
of the three thousand dollar group
coaching program you sell them on a
fifteen thousand dollar one-on-one
program that's how we have been able to
make the kind of money that we've been
able to make because if if you get just
10 people buying a fifteen thousand
dollar program after you've brought them
into your ecosystem that's a hundred and
fifty thousand dollars from just 10
people okay but going straight from just
an ad to getting somebody to give you
fifteen thousand dollars
unless you're a really really good at
sales is highly unlikely and so that's
why the Ascension model is really good
you can get good enough at sales to be
able to do that but most people out the
gate just aren't that good at sales and
their Niche is not as specific and so
that's why you're gonna dial in over
time what your Niche is you're going to
get more specific with it over time and
this is where it's kind of like the
chicken versus the egg conversation
people think about their Niche from the
wrong perspective
they think that they have to have
everything figured out before they
launch it when the truth is
you want to launch with it about
50 to 70 percent figured out
you're gonna have it like halfway
figured out and you're gonna launch it
and you're going to create a mechanism
where
what we like to do is actually have
people join a Facebook group okay and in
the Facebook group is where they get the
link
to the zoom call
and so we might create a new Facebook
group each time we do a zoom call takes
five minutes to do it so these are
throwaway Facebook groups they're not
like for building an audience we have
another Facebook group where we funnel
everybody into
we don't really do the whole like group
funnels model we don't really do that as
much but we do get people into a
Facebook group to where there's
interaction and it makes them take
action and show intent before they can
actually join the call sometimes we'll
put some pre-trainings into that
Facebook group but here's the cool part
I like about the Facebook group thing
here's the here's the great part because
the biggest part about growing
your coaching and course business is
understanding and getting into the mind
of your target Prospect
when you use a Facebook group they have
these things called group questions so
they're these questions that get asked
when people join that Facebook group and
so the reason why we use multiple groups
each time we do this is a sometimes
we'll have the same people joining each
time and we've found that the algorithm
works way better for us in our favor to
use multiple groups versus just one
group and then I can use tailor-made
very specific questions in that group
around that topic so let's say that I'm
doing a live event it's a live Zoom call
all about writing your offer copy I will
have a question in that group that says
what is your biggest struggle as it
relates to writing your offer copy and
when people join the group to access the
zoom call login
they will answer that question for me
and then I put that into a document you
can use a there's a
plugin called group convert you can look
it up group convert.com
and it actually captures all the all the
group info and pushes it over to an
Excel document you can also just copy
and paste it yourself into a Word
document that's how I've done it
um and so by doing that you're actually
able to get feedback from the people as
to what their real struggles are and so
in their words
you can actually write your offer copy
and what you'll notice is when you do
this three or four times
you're going to notice a pattern across
the board and the answers that people
give you
that is going to change what your Niche
is
because people are going to give you
feedback about how their Niche is just
slightly different than the one that
you're targeting and then you you
readjust all of your offers
to be perfectly aligned to that person
who actually joined the Facebook group
because it shows intent it shows that
they have an intention
to work with you it shows that there's
an intention to become a paid client of
yours by them being in there and so you
want to get the feedback loop going
you're getting feedback from Human
prospects you're getting feedback from
actual people
who are telling you
what they want what they care about and
what they desire and so that allows you
to hone your Niche and to dial it in to
get more specific the more specific you
are with your offers
the lower your ad cost is the higher
your profit margins are
and we've not even fully scratched the
surface of doing this in our business
and so I am very confident that we will
be hitting a seven and even eight figure
Mark in the next year or so by doing
this same process like we have with our
clients that we've worked with like Rick
Pino he started out in the niche of
worship discipleship
worship coaching all people who love
Jesus that want to worship okay but he
found that his most profitable Niche
came from worship
songwriters now not everybody who wants
to worship is a songwriter but everybody
who ended up joining his events and his
programs they ended up being songwriters
and the ones that were actually spending
money with him were songwriters and then
he dialed it in even more neither they
weren't just songwriters but they were
songwriters who had written a number of
songs
even published their songs but weren't
getting traction with them and became
frustrated by that
and as soon as he was able to dial in
deeper and deeper and deeper he started
with the broad niche of worship
discipleship but as soon as he dialed in
deeper and deeper and deeper
around those frustrated songwriters
he was able to make a million dollars in
one month selling his coaching
and the cost on ad spent was like ten
thousand dollars like that's that's a no
that makes sense it's a no-brainer you
would do that if you could invest ten
thousand dollars in ads and generate a
million dollars in return I mean ever
you would do that all day long right and
and that's what he's continued to do and
that's what we help our our clients do
as well and so if you're saying Jeremiah
this all sounds great I still don't know
what my Niche is I still don't know
which Niche to choose again you want to
answer who do you want to help what
problem do they have what solution do
you offer and now here's a couple steps
that might help help you along the way
and this is what I teach people in one
of my higher level trainings is is if
you're still stuck at this point
figuring out the most profitable Niche
or or topic
what I would recommend you do is you
make a list of some of the top ideas
that you have okay
and and and maybe you don't have any
ideas
we'll get to that in a second but I want
you to make a list of your top ideas and
then what I want you to do is I want you
to actually close up
The Notebook with those ideas
and I want you to go do something fun I
want you to go do something that you
haven't done in a long time that's very
fun for you that makes you very happy
and then come back to your notebook
after doing that fun thing
after you're excited you've gotten your
mind off of it come back to the notebook
and I want you to notice
what are the two or three ideas that you
wrote down that really stand out to you
that you really feel excited if you were
doing
why do I have you do the process of
doing something fun because what it does
is it Taps your brain into a different
way of thinking it gets you out of logic
thinking
and get you into more of intuitive
thinking this is actually sort of a way
of mentally hacking yourself into being
more intuitive and listening to your
intuition more and when it comes to
building this business intuition I
believe is everything I believe it's
that that logic Falls flat logic really
doesn't produce the best results sure we
use logic when it comes to looking at
our reporting and our finances but when
it comes to how do we communicate who do
we attract as a client I think that it
comes more from the heart than it comes
from the brain and it's going to be more
of a feeling in your body of like that
feels right versus I know that that's
right and so some of you may that might
be an unlock for you is you're feeling
inside of you that you want to do
something as a niche but you're not
quite sure if it's the right one yet I
would I would be
willing to say 99 of the time
that whatever you're feeling
excited about as a niche to do that's
actually probably going to be the one
that you're gonna be the most successful
with
and so when we actually get out of our
thinking mind out of our logic brain and
into what feels exciting for us to do
it actually becomes more profitable
now there is a aside to that is then you
want to actually rank it and look at
okay of this
will this group of people be willing to
pay me money or is there a subset of
this group of people
that would be willing to pay me money so
for instance Health coaching
there's a lot of people that want to
have their health improved
but the people that are willing to
invest ten fifteen thousand dollars
are usually more wealthy people they're
more
well-off Financial people because they
they're willing to actually throw money
out at something
to gain speed and to gain clarity and so
a lot of our clients have success in the
health Niche when they stop trying to
help the little Mom and Pops and
everybody else and they focus more on
who has a lot of expendable cash flow
and so you want to really think about
that as well when it comes to your Niche
is Expendable cash flow now obviously
you can finance things for people and
create financing options if you have a
more of a lower cost item you can
finance things for people to where they
can make payments of 300 to 500 a month
for whatever it is that you're offering
we do that often with our coaching
but you're going to still need to find
people that actually have money to spend
you're not going to be able to pressure
somebody without cash to Pony up cash
like this is it's a waste of your time
and so the what makes it most profitable
is you think about okay who are the
people that are have Expendable income
that want to solve a problem by throwing
money at something and and that helps
you identify if it's a profitable Niche
or not and this is where it all dials
into your own mindset because if you
don't believe that you're good enough
for people
to pay money to you won't sell anything
your income is directly related to your
self-belief and how much you believe
that you're worth for people to pay I'm
here to tell you today that you are a
hundred and ten percent without changing
anything that you're doing every single
person listening to this right now I say
this from experience is good enough to
be able to charge 500 to a thousand
dollars for a course or a course with
some q a
in this economy any problem that you
solve you can package
as a course or coaching program for 500
to a thousand dollars and do so very
ethically
now as it goes into you charging ten
thousand and fifteen thousand I would
say that there is more to do to do with
like are you really delivering those
results the reason why I feel confident
in what I charge people thirty thousand
dollars to work with me is I know that
they're going to get above and beyond
that
when they pay for coaching with me when
they pay for one-on-one a VIP day with
me
but it all starts with you saying okay
who do I want to help what problem do I
solve
and then doing some market research on
who else out there is solving this
problem for people and this is something
that again you need to not avoid
out of not wanting it it to be
Changed by other people's things I see a
lot of coaches say well I don't want to
be influenced by somebody else's offer
I wouldn't go through their training
necessarily but I would do what Russell
Brunson calls funnel hacking your
competitors
all of our offers and all of our
successful clients have funnel hacked
other people that offer similar results
and you can do funnel hacking by looking
at who else is out there that's serving
this Market
and start to look at okay what are they
selling what are their niches one of the
best and fastest ways to do this is two
websites
amazon.com
you can literally look up a book on any
topic anything that any Niche that you
can imagine coaching on
or making a course on I guarantee you
three or four people have written a book
on that topic
and if they hadn't
then that might be a good sign that
there's not really a market for that
ditch because there's so many books out
there that are written now there's so
many articles there's so many people the
truth is that I don't think that there's
unless it's like a new technology
there's really anything that nobody
hasn't done yet and so in the coaching
and course space you're not going to be
so original in your idea and that's
actually a really good thing to realize
is you can learn from people that have
been doing it long enough and look at
their offers that they put out there to
help you decide your niche
what's going to make you unique is you
as an individual you are worth people
buying from that they would buy from you
and not somebody else because they have
a connection with you that goes far
deeper than the result that you offer
now another great website to look at is
answerthepublic.com
answer it's all one word answer the
public.com and what you can do is when
you do some of this research on Amazon
you can go to
answerthepublic.com and you can type in
your Niche idea
and then answer the public will find
different questions that people have
asked about that idea this will help you
come up with offer ideas
you can click on the questions and it
pulls up Google results
where people typed in those questions
and then gives you who else is out there
that's serving people to solve that
problem and this will give you great
ideas for your offers and so this
process of doing some market research
using Amazon
answerthepublic.com is absolutely
invaluable to you and when you start to
do this you have to look at these
different topics you're going to start
to see advertisements pop up on your
news feed about these topics so by doing
the market research about a niche topic
you're going to see service providers
other coaches mentors and trainers that
serve the similar Niche they're going to
run ads to you and then you can click on
their ads don't be afraid of doing that
don't be like I don't want to cost them
money it's not how ads work you're not
actually going to cost the money by
clicking on it so don't worry about that
click on their ads check out their
offers what I like to do is I'll create
a swipe file where I copy and paste
their whole offer and landing page to an
Evernote document for later research so
I might have 10 to 20 different
competitors in my Niche and I'll have
their offers in front of me as I'm
developing my offer because it helps jog
my memory and come up with unique ideas
that fit my audience
now the last resource is again jasper.ai
jasper.ai is what we use for everything
and it's great for market research
because you can also ask Jasper
questions about the target Niche and
about what profitable marketing angles
you can take to Market this we have a
number of videos on using Jasper AI we
have a number of trainings in my
coaching program we teach you how to
write your sales copy using Jasper AI
you don't need to be an excellent writer
you just learn to use the artificial
intelligence and it's as easy as using a
Word document by having it generate copy
that connects with your Target customer
here's what I'll leave you with if all
of this is still overwhelming to you I
would ask you this question what got you
into the idea of making a course or
coaching program
if your answer is well I just want to
make money
I'd say it might be better if you
actually go get a job
or really create a why that's bigger
than that
if your why is just making money you're
gonna have a very hard time really going
through the process of what it actually
takes to make money in this business
so you have to actually have a real
connection a real heart connection with
your prospect with your Target customer
to be able to create offers that they
want and when you do this when you
actually have a real heart connection
with your target Prospect everything
else falls into place much faster and
much easier
the other thing is
if you're worried about choosing the
wrong Niche you're worried about wasting
time losing money
it not working out
let's not focus on the worry and let's
look at what are we creating and realize
that the process isn't always going to
be perfect from the start but it's worth
it to go through the process it might
take you some time but it's going to be
worth it but the number one activity
that you don't want to avoid and you
want to make sure that you're doing is
getting people on your email list and
getting them in front of you on Zoom
calls
that you can connect and communicate
with them
if you're still dealing with that worry
and fear and maybe and I know not
everybody deals with that but if you're
still dealing with that worry and fear
of choosing the wrong idea you might
want to ask yourself
what am I so afraid of why am I afraid
of it being the wrong idea what do I
think is going to happen and why is that
result that I'm worried about so
devastating
usually that's going to be connected to
some kind of a past experience that you
had where you made a mistake and bad
things happen because you made a mistake
realize that this isn't that same time
and that this is part of the process and
that you're growing and that you're
learning and that part of being a
student in this industry see we have
this idea that as coaches and course
creators we need to be these experts
right
you don't have to be an expert and
listen you're not an expert marketer you
don't need to be you're a student of
marketing and you're a student of
learning how to actually get your
clients a lot of the clients I work with
are are very smart on what they teach
but they are terrible at actually
crafting offers to get clients until
they go through the training that I
teach and that's normal because you
weren't taught how to create persuasive
offers it's different than knowing about
what you coach on to create offers that
actually attract clients and so give
yourself Grace to realize that you're in
the learning process of getting better
at this and it's all about taking what
is your vision what is your message and
how do you effectively communicate it to
your target Prospect how do you
effectively communicate what it is that
you want to get across to the people
that will be eventually your buyers now
how do you know that they're going to be
your buyers well this is why chicken or
the egg you can't pre-plan yourself into
success you can't map out the perfect
course enough for you to actually
succeed in this process you have to
actually get out there get some people
in front of you that you can teach that
you can coach that you can mentor and
experiment on them have them be your
beta test group have them be your
experiment group to see what kind of
results they can get so that you can
hone in and so that you can dial it in
even more a lot of my early clients I
was experimenting my methodology on and
now we've dialed it in so much and
that's why we charge what we do because
it works because that's not on trial and
it gets results
listen if you're a coach if you're a
trainer if you're a mentor
and you want to actually start to grow
your business you want to launch and
grow and get clients and make six
figures we do Live Events all the time
where I walk you through that process I
also have a group coaching program where
I provide the support and the
accountability that's going to take you
from just having an idea to getting
results in your business called the
client growth accelerator where you get
to ask questions of me where you get to
join group calls where you get all of my
courses I have a number of courses on
every topic in this process from your
funnels to your copywriting to your
advertising to creating your course to
becoming a better Coach it's all in
there for you you just have to join the
client growth accelerator and if the
doors are closed to it you can join the
waiting list and you'll be the first to
know when the doors open up again to
that all right if you're a coach if
you're a trainer if you're a mentor
don't get stuck
because you're not making a decision on
your niche
choose something
even if you can't guarantee it's perfect
there is no such thing as certainty and
guarantees in this business
you have to actually get out there get
some people on your email list get some
people to join you for a zoom call get
some people in front of you
and make mistakes make a mess learn a
lot about the process you're not going
to learn this just textbook you're going
to learn it by actually doing
unfortunately
it saddens me about this fact but
99 of coaches and mentors never actually
take action on their goals they're stuck
just figuring out their Niche because
they they can't make a decision they are
incapable of making a decision and and
it's different for everybody why that is
but as soon as you can learn to make
decisions and be okay with those
decisions not being perfect
you become okay with those decisions
being
80 to 90 percent there or fifty to
seventy percent of the way complete and
you put yourself out there
and you get leads and you get prospects
and you stop worrying about looking like
a pro and you stop worrying about
sounding like a pro and you just say I
would just want to experiment on a group
of people this is all a test
just to see what happens that's where
success follows
and so if you're a coach if you're a
trainer if you're a mentor I want to
invite you
to come on this journey to start to take
action to pick
one to two to three ideas here's the
other cool thing about picking a
profitable niche as you might have three
ideas for a niche what I usually find to
people like I really want to do all
three of these you can actually find
ways to combine all three into one
target Prospect
maybe somebody who wants
health
spiritual coaching and nutrition
coaching and you provide them with a
holistic system
to live their best life
and and but your main focus might be
around their physical body or their
Fitness or what they're putting in their
body
you see what I'm saying so you can
combine a lot of this together
to get results you don't have to be
perfect when you launch but you just
have to launch and that's the key to
success
all right everybody if this podcast has
helped you again share it with somebody
there's over 190 episodes there's a
thousand videos on YouTube there's no
reason for you to be stuck a lot of
people say I'm stuck building my
coaching and course business because
nobody ever taught me the skills well
here's the thing I'm giving you the
skills for free on YouTube in my podcast
so check those out grow your life
everybody we'll talk soon have a good
one